export const quizData = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: ` What command is used to start the React local development server? ?`,
      options: [`npm serve`,`npm run dev`,`npm start`,`npm build`],
      answer: `npm start`
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: `What is the default local host port that a React development server uses?`,
      options: [`3000`, `5000`, `8080`,`3500`],
      answer: `3000`
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: `To develop and run React code, Node.js is required.`,
      options: [`False`, `True`],
      answer: `True`
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: `Which keyword creates a constant in JavaScript?`,
      options: [`constant`, `const`, `let`,`var`],
      answer: `const`
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: `A copy of the 'real' DOM that is kept in memory is called what?`,
      options: [`virtual DOM`, `Shadow DOM`, `DOM`,`React DOM`],
      answer: `virtual DOM`
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: `React component names must begin with an uppercase letter.`,
      options: [`False`,`True`],
      answer: `True`
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: `Which operator can be used to conditionally render a React component?`,
      options: [`&&`, `??`, `::`,`||`],
      answer: `&&`
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: `When rendering a list using the JavaScript map() method, what is required for each element rendered?`,
      options: [`index`, `data`, `key`,`id`],
      answer: `key`
    },{
      id: 9,
      question: `What tool does React use to compile JSX?`,
      options: [`Babel`, `JSX compiler`, `React Router`,`ReactDOM`],
      answer: `jsx compiler`
    },
    {
    id: 10,
      question: `What is the correct command to create a new React project?`,
      options: [`npx create-react-app`, `npx create-react-app myReactApp`, `npm create-react-app`,`npm create-react-app mrReactApp`],
      answer: `npx create-react-app myReactApp`
    }
  ];
  